-Thanks for your hard work.
-You're welcome.
Bye. Why is the pretty one not here today?
Why do you ask?
Careful now.
Her lover's right next to you.
That way.
Oh.
Hey, who are you guys anyway?
How can I help you?
-What do you know about Yuan Tao?
-It's impenetrable.
Advisers like me can't profit from it.
Investors are getting out of stocks now
and buying up cryptocurrency.
They caused that.
Yuan Tao set up a separate company
called Tolita. You know it?
-So they're related.
-Yep.
You both do the same job. You run scams.
No wonder they could
set up shop in a prime location.
We wanna scam Tolita,
and we need your help.
After it's done, you'll get a big cut.
So the plan is to scam a competitor.
They know what they're doing. Big job.
I'll need my deposit up front.
Send the money to my account
within three days.
Money's no issue.
New waves pushed the old ones ahead.
Speaking as an old one,
it is indeed an honor
to learn from the new.
Huh?
Don't scam us, all right?
There is an exciting
investment opportunity
known as Do Bit.
We've all heard that, since 2009,
Bitcoin has experienced tremendous growth.
In 2024, it broke the $100,000…
THE FIXERS
DIAMOND ICE
A little while ago,
a friend who's a seafood supplier
sent a link to an investing influencer.
I looked online,
and she seemed to check out.
She teaches classes
to students focusing on cryptocurrency.
Says she's using
the teach-men-to-fish method.
She draws you in,
then gives you a taste of success.
She gives you
a small amount of free cryptocurrency
that you can invest by using their app.
Then they drive up the price,
so it looks like you're making a profit.
-Four Circles.
-Pung.
Later, I discovered
she didn't give us any fishing rods
or even any fish.
I was the target.
Why did I take the hook? Ugh.
-Six Circles.
-And pung.
-Are you listening to this?
-Yeah, who says I'm not?
Later, I discovered
the app was also a fake.
That graph was a lie.
And when I said I wanted to sell,
you know what she told me?
"Oh, I'm so sorry. Our system is down."
Then she had the nerve to say,
"Now we've frozen your account."
From what I'm hearing,
every con is identical to the other.
Look. Nine.
I win. Thanks for your support, buddy.
Actually, it wasn't just me.
A lot of my seafood clients
also got caught up in it.
That's not right.
What's not right? It's no real surprise.
You're a terrible player.
From his discards,
it's clear where he messed up.
You discard a tile
and gave him the winning one.
-Why?
-Yeah, why?
What I meant was, if the app's fake,
it's not impossible no one saw.
I was listening, all right.
You're very good at memorizing tiles,
aren't you?
In the moment,
everyone just wants to make money,
and then it turns out
the whole thing's a lie.
It's not like you're any different.
You happily discarded the wrong tile,
and then… he wiped you out.
Hey.
Why are you asking about this?
Just because.
We're running a campaign
for staff about fraud.
Oh, good for you!
You should take it.
Hey, now don't make me look bad
in front of your boss.
Don't be embarrassed. You really need it.
Why do you need to see me so suddenly?
Uh, I wanted to check how you were going
with the search for Gerald.
That's what this is about.
I thought I was in trouble.
Oh, well, we found out
the founder of Yuan Tao, Zoe,
was linked to Gerald.
And the time of Zoe's death coincides
with the disappearance of Gerald.
We also found out
that Zoe and her partner William
had a falling out.
We're working on a way
of getting close to William.
I assume you have a plan.
William has set up another company
called Tolita that runs scams.
We wanna use Tolita
to find proof of his fraud.
Then we can force him
to tell us more about Zoe.
Ah.
Uh, I heard from Fixer Gold
that Gerald is connected
to the survival of Ching He.
Uh, is that right?
There are two types of people
in this world who are the most dangerous.
Yeah.
First type possess crucial information.
The second type
are those who know what they shouldn't.
Oh, then pretend I never raised it.
I wanna live a little longer.
I'll go now.
Pretend I never asked.
ZOE
Oh. Hey, Ben.
Did you open the arcade
or the stall first?
-This stall was left to me by my father.
-Mm.
-He passed, and then I took it over.
-Oh.
The arcade I took on after I retired.
What did you do before?
Mina hasn't said anything?
I was once a fixer.
-You were a fixer? She didn't say.
-Mm-hmm.
We haven't said more than ten words
to each other. You think she's difficult?
Don't you think bad-mouthing people
behind their backs is improper?
The usual?
Hmm.
What's the usual?
Tien-bu-la. No pork meatballs or radish.
If you don't want pork or radish,
why have tien-bu-la?
If she doesn't want it, I'll have it.
There you are. Want some?
Oh, sure.
-What would you like?
-Tien-bu-la.
No blood pudding. No deep-fried tofu.
For crying out loud.
Are difficult people always picky eaters?
Young these days.
They don't eat this. They don't eat that.
-It's a pain in the ass.
-Hey.
Don't use two bowls. Just combine them.
-Combine.
-Yeah, just do what I say.
Here. There was just one bowl left.
You two can make do. Eat together.
Eat together.
This app already shows a 15% profit.
You're a fast mover.
You've already invested.
I bought it.
I got Ben to contact the crypto dealers
and convert the money into Bitcoin.
And I've downloaded the app. Look here.
Ben's graph is trending lower
than mine is, having not bought in.
That's not right.
If they wanna scam people,
then buyers should see
a significant price increase.
Gradual increases are the way.
Quick increases encourage people
to cash out their profits.
This con relies on the knowledge
that mostly earning less hurts more.
It's the law of greed.
Looks like a stroll to heaven.
Turns out to be
a one-way ticket to prison.
Hey. This just proves
that Tolita runs scams.
But it still doesn't connect back
to William.
This Dolly's
not just a spokesperson or a figurehead.
She's essentially running the whole thing.
-We need to lure William out.
-Uh…
Then we need an even bigger mark.
Yeah.
Don't look at me.
I'm already five million in debt.
Thirty million.
Oh fuck.
HUNG KUO-LUNG'S INVESTMENT PHILOSOPHY
RESUME
Next, we need to get Hung Kuo-lung
to get Dolly to believe
that you're an easy mark.
I have to ask, Mr. Hung.
Why are you working for commission
as a broker
when you're an investment adviser?
It's a sad story.
My mother passed away.
It's been two weeks.
I… I really…
Uh, I really can't continue
managing my members' accounts,
but I don't want to let them down either.
What will be your commission?
15%.
I've never had a request like this one.
I'm gonna have to think about it.
10%?
It's not the percentage,
but thanks for the suggestion.
DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES
I got the feeling
she noticed something was off.
She knew I was lying to her.
I could see it in her eyes.
That's what we want.
To think you're lying.
Huh?
We want her to find out
that you're an investment fraudster.
Because a goose that's already plucked
makes an easy meal.
The work's been done.
How could she resist making a move?
Oh. You three hustlers hired a hustler
to hustle a bigger hustler.
Impressive, and you're the goose.
Oh, here. Get rich.
-Hey.
-I win.
South Wind, Four Seasons,
and single tile weight.
I fleeced you.
Still think you can win?
Eat me.
Yeah.
Hello. Is this Mr. Chiang Ming-shun?
Sorry, wrong number.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Am I speaking with Mr. Chiang?
Ah, I'm so sorry.
Uh, the reception was terrible just now.
Hi, I'm Dolly. I'm the CEO of Tolita.
Oh, yes, I heard.
Uh, my investment manager, Hung Kuo-lung,
wants me to invest in your Do Bit.
Uh, but why are you
contacting me directly?
Because, sir, you're in
the highest investment tier with us.
This is an invitation
for you to join us at a private dinner.
Oh, there's no need for that.
I'm very interested in your product,
and I don't want to waste your time
with socializing.
How about, uh, if you need anything,
have your boss contact me directly
or come find me.
Oh, sorry. I have to board a plane.
Let's talk later.
Mr. Chiang, let me explain. You there?
Are you catching a plane?
Me, no. Uh…
-Did you see a doctor?
-My stomach's been bad.
I've got the runs.
You hate taking drugs.
You won't even see a doctor.
What drugs are they?
It's so annoying, but the doctor said
I have to take this medication.
If you won't say…
-Mom!
-Oh.
-Mom, Dad--
-Sh!
All right.
I'm going to tell you,
but you must never tell your mother.
Okay.
Ah…
You saw it.
Truth is…
-I keep shaking.
-Uh-huh.
Look.
Why is this happening?
Here, not here.
I know. I'm looking over here.
Have you heard of Parkinson's disease?
Mm.
Hmm.
Sir Hong,
every day, so many
come to pray to the deities.
Just how many people
will receive his help?
Heaven helps those who help themselves.
People who come here
believe that holding a stick of incense
and chanting a few words
will solve everything.
Hmm.
You've been here for many years,
but you're not a believer.
That's very interesting.
I just don't believe that God
or the Buddha would help people like that.
Those who take heaven's grace
should have exhausted all effort.
So in your opinion,
apart from Fixer Terra,
who else will stand with us?
Whose side they stand on doesn't matter.
But
if Tristan Hsueh is successful,
then we have an issue.
The Hsuehs are
a prominent political family.
They've made powerful relationships,
have financial resources as well.
Also, they have strong connections
with the police.
Once Yeh Yueh Tong and the Hsueh clan
join forces and grow stronger,
you will have to accept heaven's will.
Even so,
I think I still have the Hsuehs in check.
A single pawn
can't decide the chess match.
And whether this pawn is white
or black is uncertain.
At first, there was just one,
but God sent another.
You sent them to find Gerald.
Is this the right move?
I've done all I can,
and now it's heaven's will.
Hey, buddy.
Do you really think
what I said to Dolly wasn't too harsh?
If I've upset her,
the danger is she won't call back.
You're in a stronger position
if you play hard to get.
Over the years,
I've learned that if you let them go,
they actually run away.
Hey, are you playing hard to get
with Mina?
I'm telling you,
don't drag it out for too long.
-In the early days--
-You must be dressed.
-I'm done.
-Why aren't you out here?
You like?
A goose with flair.
Like an old man at a wedding banquet.
Come on. Why are you wearing this tie?
It looks good. It was the first gift
my wife ever gave me.
And your hairstyle.
Why does it look like it's 50 years old?
Because I've been doing it
for nearly 50 years.
And your gut. You need to sort that out.
-Change into something else.
-Come on, buddy.
This is the tenth one I've tried.
Never mind. I'm gonna take you somewhere.
I'm sure you're going to enjoy it.
Ya!
Hi. Hsien not here? Is he off today?
-Felix!
-Huh?
-I can't believe you're here.
-Yeah.
My father's been dead for three years.
-Is that so?
-Yeah.
Oh, I like your son's suit.
-My son? That's a stretch.
-Yeah.
-My son's in junior high.
-Ah.
So, Hsien… How did it happen?
Uh, he had a stroke,
then passed away two or three years later.
-Is that so?
-Uh-huh.
-I guess it's been ten years.
-Mm.
I am a colleague of his.
I'm here to help pick a suit.
Oh, okay.
-Let's do it.
-All right.
Who are you working for now?
Uh, I'm freelancing, I suppose.
-Oh.
-Uh-huh.
182, 94, 86, 94.
-Oh.
-He's been touching me.
Eight times already.
-Time flies.
-Sure does.
I remember when we were younger?
You and she would bring alcohol as a gift.
I wanted a drink, but you wouldn't let me.
Here. Try this one on.
Who told you
not to let Chi chase you back then?
Ten years have gone
in the blink of an eye.
Your dad's gone. Chi's gone too.
That rack?
They were custom-made for mobsters
back in the day.
That's why it's all the same design.
This one's very Felix Chiang.
Oh, he used to hate wearing this style.
He used to have them specially made
by my dad.
It's the thing to have custom-made.
He keeps saying he used to be a gangster,
was a crack shooter, and was feared.
That right?
Felix and Chi were known
as the Black and White Impermanence.
Cold Blood was a crack shot.
Chi was the fighter.
Cold Blood?
Yeah, he chose that.
How did he turn into such a smooth talker?
To survive in that world,
you had to be like that.
Hey.
Can you two stop bad-mouthing me
while I'm getting changed?
Ah, if nothing had happened to Chi
back then,
maybe the two of them
would still be prowling the streets.
Here. What do you think?
Is it all right?
-Huh?
-Oh gosh. You look so good, Felix.
-Finally.
-Let me see.
How's the waistline?
No need to alter it. It's perfect.
-What about the length?
-It's okay. I'm your average man.
You forgot your clothes.
I don't need them. Hmm?
THE GENTLEMAN'S SUIT SHOP, PREMIUM SUITS
Mr. Chiang.
Hi. Come sit down here.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Did you bring the manager?
He's a crypto dealer. I run Tolita.
You have no one above you? So you're it?
Mm-hmm. Yes, I run Tolita.
Mm.
And so young.
Ah. Shall we eat?
Um…
Do you think it's unusual
that I chose this place for the meeting?
Any place is good to discuss investments.
Right.
My business actually started right here.
It was 20 years ago on this very spot.
I had nothing.
I could only order one plate of swamp eel
with no swamp eel.
Then you know what I overheard
at the next table?
They were talking about
how to venture abroad.
Hung Kuo-lung is involved
in stock scams. Stay away from him.
I know. That's why I asked elsewhere.
I called Dubai and asked around.
Reading through this, he smells fishy.
See what he's after.
Don't rush to commit, okay?
Mm-hmm, got it.
What about me?
When do I take over Yuan Tao?
I'm sick of lying.
Tolita needs someone like you to run it.
I only trust you.
Okay?
Mr. Chiang, I'm curious.
In Dubai, what sort of company do you run?
I developed surgical technologies.
Hmm.
Because I did a quick check,
and I couldn't find any company output
or cash flow.
Ah, I should tell you.
The tech company's a front.
My real business is… games of chance.
-Ah.
-You get me.
No wonder I couldn't find anything.
I've always wanted to invest.
I don't want others saying
that I'm just a gambler
who relies on luck.
Mr. Chiang.
At Tolita, we do detailed searches
of every investor.
Because, as you know, this is fairer
and safer for every investor.
You don't believe me.
-I wanna be frank with you.
-Mm.
I have a few business contacts in Dubai.
No one there
has ever heard of your business.
Take a look, will you?
I know how much you like cash.
Am I right?
Hey, I trust you won't make
a mess of this.
Mr. Chiang, you can trust us.
All right. Dig in.
The flavors haven't changed in 20 years.
Come on. Don't be shy.
I really rattled that guy,
so he had to roll out the loot.
I tell you, that influencer was afraid
I didn't have the money.
Once she saw the cash, she was all mine.
She took it, we signed a contract,
and she showed me the app.
I'm taking the cash to launder it.
I'll find you later.
She's taking her spoils
to a money launderer now.
Mm.
We're following her car.
Oh, hey.
When you two are done tailing her,
just get here.
I ordered too much. I can't finish it.
I'll even leave you two
to eat alone, okay?
We were once so close, and now this.
All right, I'll eat it myself.
For you.
How did you know
I only eat these two things?
I didn't.
They're just the two things I don't eat.
The money launderer is here.
Why not take it
to the black market and swap it for gold?
They'll convert the money
into internationally accepted crypto,
then put it in Dolly's overseas account.
This way of handling,
it's more confidential.
Just because they met with that launderer
doesn't tie in William.
How much money have you made
in your phone app?
Around 4%. Like you said, slowly growing.
Then I think it's time for us to shine.
That investment last time,
I did see some profit.
And I'm not pulling out.
Uh, let's see if we can grow some more.
As a businessman,
you know what long-term holding can yield,
but you should think about
supplementing it.
It'll increase your earnings.
I think that as well,
but I found a target for my investing.
This company got me 40%
in next to no time.
He got 40.
How is that possible? You sure?
You just can't do that well at the moment.
Look, this is their invitation.
It's a Singaporean company,
but other than that,
there's no other information.
It's gotta be a scam.
Go check it out.
There'll be a lot of investors.
You could take a few from them.
Mm-hmm.
This is your last task.
Invite your investment clients
to a party we're having.
That'll be easy.
But you think William will take the bait?
We'll find out.
This is not all the…
I'll definitely need your advice.
Hey, this is the CEO.
For someone so young,
she has an amazing understanding
of finance.
I'm definitely gonna need your help.
You can just call me Mandy.
-All right. Let's keep talking. Cheers.
-Absolutely. Okay.
-Cheers. We'll talk later.
-Stay in touch. Okay.
-Bye now.
-Bye-bye.
Hi. My name's Dolly. I run Tolita.
-Tolita?
-Yes.
Mm, hello.
You know, that snack you introduced me to
was delicious.
-Really?
-Mandy.
-I wanted to say hello.
-Hi.
The Hsueh family's youngest son,
Louis Hsueh.
-Oh, hello.
-Hello.
Just like your brother. Good-looking guy.
Power is his thing while I'm into money.
Ah. How long you been a member?
A bit over a month.
I've already made a little.
-Ah, you're still very young.
-Yes.
I'll leave you to chat.
There's a chairman coming.
I need to greet him.
In due course.
I'll share some derivatives with you.
-Great.
-Bye.
-Hey.
-That suit looks good on you.
Took a while to choose it.
Hi. Could I steal a cigarette?
I'm all out.
You here to steal investment clients?
What are you talking about?
Trading cryptocurrencies.
Isn't that what you do?
You're some performer.
Every client inside
is worth hundreds of millions.
I won't be handing them over.
You stole one of my investors.
That's why I came.
I didn't steal him.
That guy made his own decision.
You're a new business,
yet you have so many clients.
Are you a front for someone?
We operate legally.
If you wanna know the way,
I'd be happy to share it with you.
The truth is,
our company works with Yuan Tao.
One of its founders, William,
he's also a shareholder.
If you'd like to join us,
we can share the profits.
However, there are terms.
I thought you were legit.
You're a scammer.
What makes you so sure?
You can't possibly be in with Yuan Tao.
Do you know William?
So it turns out you guys have
a collaboration with Yuan Tao.
I did wonder.
Tolita is such a young company
to have seen such growth.
And haven't they discovered
that Tolita is heavily involved
in financial fraud?
Where did you hear this?
Money launderers are huge gossips.
But don't be concerned.
I'm not going to out you.
I just wanna make money.
How about this?
Now that I've shared
these clients with you,
why don't we bring William in?
The truth's out, so why not clean up?
If William doesn't know
your company's running scams,
I'll keep your secret.
And if he does,
your secret will still be safe.
And the profits I make
working with Yuan Tao,
you'll get your share.
You got a problem with that?
Was Hsueh's younger son there?
Yeah.
He claimed he made a lot of money
from investing with them.
This Mandy knows those money launderers.
She is definitely not good.
She wouldn't target him anyway.
He's too high up.
Must be targeting easy marks.
And she's using me to do it.
I can't leave her be.
Wanna meet her?
I don't need another enemy,
and there are indeed many easy targets.
But I need to confirm one thing.
We recommend long-term investment.
We also think that blockchain technology
isn't just for short-term speculation.
So, in this area,
Yuan Tao will continue to innovate.
BARRAGE OF NEGATIVE NEWS
TRIGGERS BLOODBATH IN CRYPTO MARKET!
At my advanced age,
meeting in the evening
to catch the wind is rare.
I only drink tea now.
Long time no see.
To alcohol over tea.
My father would often say
that of all the fixers,
he admired you the most.
You're always calculating,
yet you are also calm.
Please, let's skip the pleasantries.
What's there to discuss?
I know you and Thackery are close-knit.
You're hard to unstitch.
I just wanna remind you
that not taking a stand
is also taking a stand.
What if I…
I chose to take a stand?
All I know is that by not taking a stand,
all these rumors will vanish,
and your position will be secure.
All I know is,
choosing Thackery Huang
to be Fixer Celestial
was the right choice then.
But right now,
insisting on letting him stay
is not a good idea.
Don't forget Ching He's code.
Render large issues small.
The small ones will go.
Hmm.
I'm old. I can't withstand this wind.
I won't have the good fortune
to enjoy this fine wine.
I heard you invested in Hsin Yueh
and made a killing.
Aren't you a shareholder?
Mandy told me after I'd already invested.
You keep a good secret.
I'd like to learn from you.
You're independent financially,
yet retirement's not on the cards.
It's like a round of golf.
Winning someone else's money…
It's just like a game, isn't it?
It's all about the win.
Hmm? Don't you think?
Huh, nice.
I think I know what you're saying.
Okay, see you at the restaurant.
How'd it go?
William wants to talk.
You got there.
So how are you going to get him
to reveal his Tolita connection?
He now thinks I'm a scammer.
If he wants to collaborate,
Tolita has to come in.
Oh.
If he won't collaborate,
he'll ask you
not to reveal Tolita's scam activity,
which is proof that he is connected
to this company, right?
It's such a shame
that you work as a fixer.
If I'd met you sooner, damn.
The gambling joint would have thrived.
Genius.
Ah.
Felix said
you're meeting with William tomorrow.
Mm.
Tomorrow night.
What's on your mind?
This whole investigation till now.
What do I do
if the outcome's not what I want it to be?
Ben made this for you.
No radishes, no pork meatballs.
You know, if I don't order it from him,
he won't offer it to me.
Enjoy it.
What's in this for you?
Being a fixer?
If my brother ever has a problem
he can't handle,
I can help him take care of it.
Then my dad will know he has two sons.
Tomorrow will go smoothly.
You've gotten better.
Ten to seven. You're off your game today.
I thought I'd let you win today.
If you shut down because of me,
I'll have nowhere to play.
-This is for you.
-Oh, thank you.
-Ah.
-Gun for you.
-Go home and practice.
-First time I got this.
-Come on, let's eat.
-All right.
I know I haven't been here for a while,
but these prices are ridiculous.
Okay. The food all right?
Why did I win?
I should lose to you.
I'm growing old. You're growing up.
Why won't you tell Mom you're sick?
Telling her now
will only make her more worried.
I looked it up online.
Parkinson's just gets worse, you know?
Of course I know.
And so, there'll be a day
when your mom will be your responsibility.
Stop that.
Don't underrate me, okay?
I can take care of you, too,
and Mom's stronger than you think as well.
I don't need you to tell me.
When she's mad, I know to stay well away.
You should decide
what to give Mom for her birthday.
I know, and I got her a gift.
Oh.
She'll love it.
Mm. Eat quickly.
We've gotta get the sticky tofu
for your mom.
Then hurry up and get it.
Your chicken cutlet will take a while.
Yeah, good idea.
You can eat the noodles,
but the chicken cutlet is off-limits.
You hear me?
The plane ticket is booked.
Counting down to going abroad.
Don't miss me too much.
Yes, yes, okay.
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Okay, bye.
Fuck! What is that?
We'll follow party protocol.
There'll be no special consideration.
We cannot waver
due to changes in the political wind,
nor can we let an isolated incident
cloud our determination for reform.
As for my father, he is in good health.
He continues to care about society
and about people.
I'd like to thank everyone.
We now have breaking news.
Don't wait. He won't be there.
Search and rescue personnel
found the body in the mountains.
The exact cause and motive of death
are yet to be determined.
The sudden news of this tragedy
has shocked the business world.
Yuan Tao will be releasing a statement
later this evening.
Fuck!